<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__preamble_1">%1$s is an open source XMPP messenger for Android, iOS and Web platforms. It is build around open standards, interoperability, design and great user experience. Versions of %2$s for every platform are built to provide a continuous chat experience between them.</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__preamble_2">You will find more information on our official website %s</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__preamble_2__link">https://www.xabber.com</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_1__header">XMPP protocol</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_1__text">Extensible Messaging and Presence Protocol (XMPP) is a communications protocol for message-oriented middleware based on XML (Extensible Markup Language). It enables the near-real-time exchange of structured yet extensible data between any two or more network entities. The protocol was originally named Jabber, and was developed by the Jabber open-source community in 1999 for near real-time instant messaging (IM), presence information, and contact list maintenance.</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_2__header">XMPP Extension Protocols</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_2__text">XMPP is highly extensible, via extensions known as XEPs (XMPP Extension Protocol). %s supports a number of popular XEPs that are essential to providing great chat experience for our users.</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_3__header">Developers</string>
    <string name="client_developer_company_name">Redsolution</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_3__text_1">%1$s was originally developed by %2$s — an international software and services company currently based in Estonia. Since then, a number of individuals joined %3$s as developers, testers and translators.</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_3__text_2">Our goal is to create a stable, reliable, interoperable and user friendly ecosystem for instant messaging that does not rely on proprietary services and data silos. We welcome anyone who believes in open standards and free information interchange to take part in moving %s forward.</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_3__text_3">Follow us on Twitter and Github.</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_4__header">Translators</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_4__text_1">%s is available in multiple languages thanks to many fine people from all over the world. We have created a special page on our website to acknowledge their efforts.</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_4__text_2">You may join their ranks and help us improve translation quality by contributing your translations to %s</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_4__text_2__link__text">%s project</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_5__header">License</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_5__text_1__link__text">GitHub</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_5__text_1">%1$s source code is licensed under GNU AGPL v.3 license and is available on %2$s</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_5__text_2">Graphical images are licensed under Creative Commons Attribution Share-Alike (CC BY-SA) license.</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_5__text_3">%1$s &amp; %2$s logo are property of %3$s</string>
    <string name="client_developer_company_full_name">Redsolution, OÜ</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_5__text_4">View %1$s %2$s for more information.</string>
    <string name="web_client__screen_about__block_5__text_4__link__text">license file</string>
</resources>
